<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<protocol name="tdesktopenvironment_accessibility_v1">
  <copyright>
    Copyright © 2023 Victor Tran

    Permission to use, copy, modify, distribute, and sell this
    software and its documentation for any purpose is hereby granted
    without fee, provided that the above copyright notice appear in
    all copies and that both that copyright notice and this permission
    notice appear in supporting documentation, and that the name of
    the copyright holders not be used in advertising or publicity
    pertaining to distribution of the software without specific,
    written prior permission.  The copyright holders make no
    representations about the suitability of this software for any
    purpose.  It is provided "as is" without express or implied
    warranty.

    THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THIS
    SOFTWARE, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
    FITNESS, IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY
    SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES
    WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN
    AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION,
    ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF
    THIS SOFTWARE.
  </copyright>

  <description summary="accessibility">
    This protocol allows a privileged client to turn on HID accessibility features.
  </description>

  <interface name="tdesktopenvironment_accessibility_sticky_keys_v1" version="1">
    <enum name="modifier">
      <description summary="Modifier keys">
        These values indicate modifier keys that can be latched by Sticky Keys
      </description>

      <entry name="shift" value="1" />
      <entry name="control" value="4" />
      <entry name="alt" value="8" />
      <entry name="super" value="64" />
    </enum>

    <request name="set_enabled">
      <description summary="set enabled">
        Sets whether Sticky Keys is enabled or disabled.
      </description>
      <arg name="enabled" type="uint" summary="Whether Sticky Keys is enabled or disabled"/>
    </request>

    <event name="sticky_keys_enabled">
      <description summary="sticky keys enabled changed">
        The event tells the client that the activation state of Sticky Keys has changed.
      </description>
      <arg name="enabled" type="uint" summary="Whether Sticky Keys is enabled or disabled"/>
    </event>

    <event name="sticky_keys_held">
      <description summary="sticky keys held changed">
        The event tells the client that the keys that Sticky Keys is holding has changed.
      </description>
      <arg name="keys" type="uint" enum="modifier" summary="The keys that Sticky Keys is holding"/>
    </event>

    <event name="sticky_keys_latched">
      <description summary="sticky keys latched changed">
        The event tells the client that the keys that Sticky Keys has latched has changed.
      </description>
      <arg name="keys" type="uint" enum="modifier" summary="The keys that Sticky Keys has latched"/>
    </event>
  </interface>
</protocol>
